Thump, thump, thump!
Good morning
good morning
What? What?
Did you sleep in?
Good morning. Good morning.
I've changed since I left the stage
I've changed since I left the stage.
My head is longer.
What's out of your head?
My head has grown.
He's taller than me.
I heard there's a whole bamboo shoot in it.
So cute!
Yesterday, I told Shiji about the live broadcast.
And today, after that...
I got this from Jeriah.
I put on my phone shoulder.
So cute!
Good morning.
I finished my makeup.
Look. I wanted to eat this. Salad Hope.
I got it.
What a specialty of Niigata.
A snack. Salad Hope.
And, what's this?
Some kind of soup.
Tare Katsu-don!
Tarekatsudon is here!
It looks like tarekatsudon for lunch.
Made with water?
Yes, it is. This is kind of warm.
Can I have this too?
Grains of tea dumplings.
Tarekatsu-don. It is a tarekatsu bento.
Canned soup with almost all ingredients.Canned soup with almost no ingredients.
TELELAY!!!
Amazing!
We received a lot of food.
Oh no! Such a lot!
Everyone is already in a cute state.
It's amazing! So many!
Good boy!
Amazing!
Cake sticks.
We found them at Salad Hawk over there.
They were delicious. I tried it.
Langdosha.
Two salad hawks.
There's also a little dumpling.
There are also these little dumplings.
Various kinds of Sasadanko.
Amazing.
There are three salad hawks.
Only two of them are broken.
Look! Land oyster sauce. I wanted to eat it.
Is this a dream?
Yes.
Niigata Scramble.
Full today.
Thank you.
Bon appétit.
I'm glad.
Gaga dango.
Congratulations.
I, I'm currently on stage, good! I'm performing in Hikaru Harajuku.
Yay!
I finished the first day yesterday and came to Niigata.
Yesterday, I had an interview before the first day.Yesterday, I had an interview, before the first day.
I was too nervous for the interview,
I was too nervous, and after I said my name, "I play the role of 00," everyone was talking about their enthusiasm for the first day of the show,
I was so nervous that I forgot to say my name,
I just said my enthusiasm,
I was a little nervous,
I was a little nervous, but the first day went well.
Of course, I know there were many of you who came to see the first day of the show yesterday,
Thank you very much.
The role is different from that of an idol,
I think I show a side of myself that I don't usually show,
I hope you all enjoy it,
I hope that everyone will enjoy it and feel the atmosphere or the realism of the scene.
But today is the Niigata performance, so I will do my best again with a renewed spirit.
To the number 2 person, to the number 6 person, to the number 6 person, tiny.
Please do.
Please take care of me.
Please.
Paper.
You're a bad hand, huh?
Yumia, the bottom hand, takes the stairs on the way home.
Yes.
Same place.
Elevator on the way back, too.
I'm sorry. The bottom of the stairs.
There are a lot of stairs.
There are a lot of holes.
It's okay.
Just there.
Okay.
Then we're together.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Bye bye.Bye-bye.
Well, I'm going up.
I'm going to take the stairs down.
It's very hot to go up, but you can go down.
Good shed ok how is the summer ground deadly
aire
beijing
notice for next time
my daily life too
ghost beach get
Ikejump
Date Sabada
You turned 20, right?
That's right, both of us.
That's 22, both of us.
First time.
I've been in Japan for a long time.
That's right.
It's been a long time since I was in Indonesia.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
Niigata.
That's good.
Hey. Niigata.
Seriously.
Seriously, it was good.
It is Niigata.
Yesterday's birthday.
Yes.
We went out a lot.
Thank you very much.
Even to Ebisu Station,
Hey. I want to see it with you.
I saw an ad at Ebisu station yesterday.
There was an ad.The ads.
Yes, yes.
Already, everyone going down the escalator,
You know, they're looking at the face of the horse race,
while looking a little far away.
Because, you know, I saw it when I was taking pictures.
They are making a lot of penthouses.
You know.
Pento only for dreams.
Masuo Sakiyama. What's that?
It's Masuo Sakiyama.
It's Masuo Sakiyama-san.
Hey.
Hot?
Hot.
What time do we start filming?
Koshihikari.
It's a sake bento made with Koshihikari.
Wow! It's magnificent!
It looks so delicious.
Looks delicious.
Let's eat.
Let's eat. Let's eat.
Sorry, but it looks delicious.
Jangan!
Please flip over here and check the area.
Now, I'd like to flip it over.
Now, can you guess the winner?
Missed!
Aki-chan, it's your turn!
Jajajajajajajan!
Yes!
Missed!
See you later!
Yes!
But, even if it's off this way, look at me.But hey, even if it's off this way, look at me.
It's so dekar!
So cute!
It works!
Oh, you don't mind?
It's so cute!
It's cute.
It's cute!
This one's good, too!
Here's exciting, here's cute!
Everyone is smiling!
Everyone is thrilled and excited as they open the package,
But the only ones that come our way are the losers.
Hey!
Chiririn!
No, that's not true.
If you get one, you can join the farewell party.
Really?
Yay!
That makes five of you.
Ta-da!
I've chosen Mr. Sasa's Koshin!
Oh, that one? This one? Would you have eaten it if it wasn't this way? Koshin.
It's a new shape.
But I only know this one.
I've never eaten the other one before.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Ah!
Mellow.
So soft, so soft, so soft!
I thought bamboo grass dumplings
I thought they were a Fukushima sweet.
My grandmothers are from Fukushima.
I had an image that they were sold in Fukushima.I had an image that they were sold in Fukushima.
Like a day station in Fukushima.
The way it looks
Very mochi mochi (sticky rice cake)
I'll do my best again today!
Next time
Extra
Next time preview
extra
Singing by way of Excemb Heart Adct 2023
Cute, cute, too cute.
Thank you very much for coming to
Super Doki Doki Green no Hi Hiko to Lying Hanami to
Super pounding green day hiko and I'm day hiko and I'm day hiko and I'm day hiko Yoshikawa.
Thank you very much.
Before we begin, a few words of caution and a few requests.
The show will begin shortly.
Today we're two. Today I'm alone.
How are you all doing?
Are you ready to get excited?
Yes, I'm fine.
Then let's have fun.
Just wait a little longer.
Hanami Junior Hanami, Boom, Boom, Alcohol, Autumn, Sunny days
Super Doki Doki Advertising Department
Lampro.
Okay, everyone, please.
Thank you for watching.
This will be a subway station from here.
This is a subway station.
Water from the road.
Encore.Encore.
Okay, let's move on.
Which way do you want to go?
I'm going to the elevator.
I'm getting shaggy.
I'm shaggy.
I was struggling earlier, and I got shaggy.
This is cute.
Well, open it up, please.
Easy, easy. Elevator.
Harry will run.
Three times.
Great.
Here we go.
Start!
Let's run!
Thank you all for coming to the park!
[Applause]
The show is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
My arms are soooo sore.
I just woke up.
I'm so tired.
Itchy stomach.
The domestic rotation is here.
Wait for it.
The Niigata concert is over.
Thank you very much.
We changed costumes and so on,
Do you recognize these costumes?
We also have a new morning costume.
I love it so much.
And the T-shirts are fresh and new.
They are so beautiful.It's so beautiful, isn't it?
I think they even changed my T-shirt.
It's so beautiful.
It's so beautiful and cute.
I was able to come to Niigata for the first time as a super thrilled Senjuus,
I hope I can come again.
I want to come again.
Cute.
I like it.
Three more performances.
First day performance.
Love love love.
Sorry to bother you.
See you soon.
Let's do our best.
Local Kanagawa.
That's right. Because we are all in Kanagawa.
Because I,
Yes, that's right. Everyone is from Kanagawa.
I'm introducing a lot of things from Kanagawa for your birthday,
So please enjoy yourselves when you come to Kanagawa.
Oh yeah.... Hito-chan bought something.
Try to buy it.
Enjoy.
It's fun, isn't it?
Yes, it is. So, I'll see you next time in Yokohama.
See you soon.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.
I will come back to Niigata.
Thank you for meeting me.
Congratulations.
Let's have cake afterwards.Let's have cake afterwards.
Looks delicious.
Bye bye.
Thank you. Congratulations.
I told you it was a badge strip music Raptor at the $1,000 store and some random song.
These are exactly the two things that remind me of the money you could sign up for at Al-Mail.
They won't let me awful the wrong music.
It's so directional.
The music video's 书书, Almere's play attack sound effects, the decorations really stand out like in England!
I wonder why, when I laugh, surely the world seems to shine
I can turn the umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
They're guiding me along
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
When it's raining, I'll try to smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools and rainbow puddles
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Lalala...
Please subscribe to our channel!